<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>&#39;Cat&#39;.concat(&#39;Man&#39;)</title>
    <description>&#39;Cat&#39;.concat(&#39;Man&#39;) is the official start-up got frisky with programming and had a djing baby blog of Reid Covington, the real CatMan.</description>
    <link>http://yourdomain.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://yourdomain.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2014 17:15:33 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2014 17:15:33 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.1.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Who&#39;s the Real CatMan</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;“Do you have a dog?” Asked the woman in the elevator. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a id=&quot;2cats&quot; title=&quot;&quot; href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;“No. I have 2 cats.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
“Oh,” she exclaimed and exchanged aroused glances with her friend. “It’s hard to find a good &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;cat man&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;…” &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wasn’t always a CatMan though. It’s been a long journey to get here. Let me give you the high-level stack-trace.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I guess it all started in a boardroom in Shanghai. I was sitting across the table from a portly Chinese entrepreneur who was saying something to the effect of “Life, is all about creation.” And I thought, &lt;em&gt;YES&lt;/em&gt;! I subsequently quit my job in finance, moved back to NYC, and started up &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.shopcube.com&quot;&gt;ShopCube.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That first year was cinematic. I had absolutely no idea what I was doing. Everyday was 20-hour-days that felt like the &lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;last 5 minutes of Zero Dark Thirty &lt;/a&gt; – where you know that Osama is gonna get wacked but the suspense of &lt;em&gt;is this shit happening for real&lt;/em&gt; is eating away at your skin… Well, it was happening for real, and it was exhilarating. I quickly discovered that taking a company from inception, to launching it with a 15,000 user-base, and doubling that user-base in the first year, all without spending a dollar on marketing got me FIRED UP - you know, &lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;never need to sleep because life is so good you can taste it in your spit &lt;/a&gt; - FIRED UP.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But I will be the first to admit that I, we, made a lot of mistakes. Too many to list. The majority of them were honest, naïve inefficiencies that we were able to address and overcome with relative ease. One crucial error in judgment, however, the negative consequences of which we are still dealing with, was the decision to outsource our development. It seems reasonable right? Neither my partner nor I had a technical background and our third partner, the CTO, lived in Israel and was confident that his Israeli team was comparable to any local talent at a quarter of the price. &lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;Sweet I thought&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Outsourcing development is singlehandedly responsible for nearly every serious pain point we’ve had at ShopCube. As a result of outsourcing development we were at the &lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;mercy &lt;/a&gt; of the Israeli dev team’s timetable, which was always at least 4-5x what they estimated. Communication, when even possible, was a never-ending source of frustration. If the site crashed, which a newly launched site of ShopCube’s complexity obviously did, we had little-to-no recourse. But none of these problems would or did sink us. They cost us a great deal of physical, financial, and emotional resources, but I don’t consider them the &lt;em&gt;real&lt;/em&gt; evil in outsourcing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When we parted ways with our CTO and moved development to the US, I took over managing the development team. While it was a step in the right direction in almost every sense and helped address all of the pain points I just mentioned, it failed to address what became obvious to me as the real evil in outsourcing development – inevitable lack of control.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Outsourcing development is like being a customer in your own restaurant. That sounds insane, right? Imagine asking someone to invest in a restaurant you’re opening and then telling him or her that &lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;you don’t know how to cook&lt;/a&gt;. As skilled a project manager, as effective a marketer, as efficient an optimizer, as creative a designer as I may be, ultimately these skills would be delegated to a product being created by someone else, someone else with inherently less passion and motivation. The tangible consequences of this are an inability to meaningfully contribute to all important technical debates and decisions. You can say, “I want this feature” and listen to the feasibility, the different potential implementations and their estimates, but you can’t really contribute. This means that a large portion of the decisions that arguably affect your product more than anything else are not being made by you. No matter how &lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;brilliant a vision you have for your restaurants menu&lt;/a&gt;, the food that comes out of the kitchen won’t be executed exactly the way you want. With such a razor thin line between success and failure in any venture do you really want to roll the dice leaving your company’s fate in the hands of someone being paid by the hour?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Life, is all about creation,” said the Chinese entrepreneur. Not “half-assed creation”, but “creation.” I helped create the start of what could be something truly incredibly at ShopCube. But I failed to be a part of some of the most important steps in its creation and I refuse to live a life of half-assed creation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Acting on this realization, I began to learn my way around the kitchen and almost a year later, after over 1,500 hours preparing for and immersed in a programming school called &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.devbootcamp.com&quot;&gt;Dev Bootcamp&lt;/a&gt;, I am proud to call myself an engineer. Not a customer in my own Kitchen, but a chef. Not a guy who owns cats, but &lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;a CatMan&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Life really is all about creation. The technical debt of my outsourced predecessors is significant, but its exhilarating and satisfying to recreate our product and be intimately involved in every decision that goes into it. And this is only the very very beginning, the absolute tip of the iceberg and &lt;a href=&quot;#&quot;&gt;a hundred other clichés&lt;/a&gt;. There is so much I want to create now that sometimes I feel like I’m going to explode.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway, I’m really glad you’re here at the beginning with me. It’s going to be one hell of a ride!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2014 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/jekyll/update/2014/07/01/who-is-the-real-cat-man/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/jekyll/update/2014/07/01/who-is-the-real-cat-man/</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Like Whatever!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;You’ll find this post in your &lt;code&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory - edit this post and re-build (or run with the &lt;code&gt;-w&lt;/code&gt; switch) to see your changes!
To add new posts, simply add a file in the &lt;code&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory that follows the convention: YYYY-MM-DD-name-of-post.ext.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jekyll also offers powerful support for code snippets:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;puts&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;Hi, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;#{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&amp;#39;Tom&amp;#39;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;#=&amp;gt; prints &amp;#39;Hi, Tom&amp;#39; to STDOUT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out the &lt;a href=&quot;http://jekyllrb.com&quot;&gt;Jekyll docs&lt;/a&gt; for more info on how to get the most out of Jekyll. File all bugs/feature requests at &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jekyll/jekyll&quot;&gt;Jekyll’s GitHub repo&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2014 14:21:02 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/jekyll/update/2014/06/30/welcome-to-jekyll/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/jekyll/update/2014/06/30/welcome-to-jekyll/</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
