<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>&#39;Cat&#39;.concat(&#39;Man&#39;)</title>
    <description>&#39;Cat&#39;.concat(&#39;Man&#39;) is the official start-ups got annotatedly frisky with programming and had a djing baby blog of Reid Covington, the real CatMan.</description>
    <link>http://yourdomain.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://yourdomain.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2014 14:14:22 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2014 14:14:22 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.1.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>&#39;Am I in?!&#39;...Implementing Google Analytics with Jekyll and verifying the implimentation</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This wasn’t my first time implementing Google Analytics, but it was my first time doing the entire process from account creation to full implementation on my own… and &lt;span class=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;easyaspie.jpg&quot;&gt;it couldn’t have been easier&lt;/span&gt; (implementing it, but verifying its implementation proved trickier, more on this later).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, create a Google Analytics account ( &amp;lt; 5min). Simply follow the steps Google provides to register your website with Google Analytics, fill in your URL (including cross/sub domain tracking if your home page is not the same as your base url; ex: if www.reidcovington.com redirected to www.reidcovington.com/index.html), create 1 simple &lt;code&gt;view&lt;/code&gt; that will be where you can view your analytics, and then Google Analytics will give you a JavaScript Snippet with your unique tracking code to embed everywhere you want GA to track:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-javascript&quot; data-lang=&quot;javascript&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;script&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;kd&quot;&gt;function&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;i&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;s&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;o&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;g&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;r&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;a&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;m&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;){&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;i&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;[&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&amp;#39;GoogleAnalyticsObject&amp;#39;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;]&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;r&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;i&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;[&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;r&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;]&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;i&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;[&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;r&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;]&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;||&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;kd&quot;&gt;function&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(){&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;i&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;[&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;r&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;].&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;q&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;i&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;[&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;r&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;].&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;q&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;||&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;[]).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;push&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;arguments&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)},&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;i&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;[&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;r&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;].&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;l&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;1&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;*&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;new&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;Date&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;();&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;a&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;s&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;createElement&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;o&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;),&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;m&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;s&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;getElementsByTagName&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;o&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)[&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;0&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;];&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;a&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;async&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;1&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;a&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;src&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;g&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;m&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;parentNode&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;insertBefore&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;a&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;m&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;})(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;window&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;document&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&amp;#39;script&amp;#39;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&amp;#39;//www.google-analytics.com/analytics.js&amp;#39;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&amp;#39;ga&amp;#39;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;);&lt;/span&gt;

      &lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;ga&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&amp;#39;create&amp;#39;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&amp;#39;UA-52973139-1&amp;#39;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&amp;#39;auto&amp;#39;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;);&lt;/span&gt;
      &lt;span class=&quot;nx&quot;&gt;ga&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&amp;#39;send&amp;#39;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&amp;#39;pageview&amp;#39;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;);&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;err&quot;&gt;/script&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To keep things modular and save yourself a lot of work, follow Google’s optional dynamic implementation advice &lt;code&gt;Use a common include or template to paste the code above instead of manually adding it to every page&lt;/code&gt;
and put your JS tracking snippet in a Jekyll’s includes file named: &lt;code&gt;_includes/google_analytics.html&lt;/code&gt;.
Finally, include your tracking code on all of the pages of your website by modifying the &lt;code&gt;file_layouts/head.html&lt;/code&gt; to include the line:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-html&quot; data-lang=&quot;html&quot;&gt;{% include google_analytics.html %}&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Note: the JavaScript code GA gives you should not be altered in any way and should be placed directly before the closing &lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;/head&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; tag per GA’s instructions. Check this by viewing your source code once implemented or &lt;span class=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;googleansource.png&quot;&gt;take a peek at mine using the developer view&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Boom, I successfully created a new GA account, set up the basic necessary account settings, and implemented GA in less time than I run a 5k (that’s less than 18:52 seconds!)! &lt;span class=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;zoolander-gas-fight-o.gif&quot;&gt;I am cookin with gas, or so I thought&lt;/span&gt;. Just to be double sure my GA was implemented properly so that Google wouldn’t miss counting the 33 times I would likely visit the site before the days end (always making sure to click a post link so as to keep my bounce rate low) I followed the steps found &lt;a href=&quot;https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/1008083?hl=en&quot;&gt;here - to make sure my tracking code had been implemented properly&lt;/a&gt;. This leads you through a process of signing into your &lt;code&gt;account&lt;/code&gt;, clicking on &lt;code&gt;admin&lt;/code&gt;, and checking the &lt;code&gt;Tracking Info/ Tracking Code&lt;/code&gt; status message to see if it says &lt;code&gt;tracking installed&lt;/code&gt; or &lt;code&gt;receiving data&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First of all, check out the super vague fucking disclaimer GA gives out in a couple different spots:&lt;br /&gt;
“It can take up to 24 hours for the Google Analytics servers to update after you make a change to your tracking code, so if you’ve recently completed or changed your set up, wait before you check to see if it’s working.”&lt;br /&gt;
Update what?! Update the analytics data? Update to my server? Or update the tracking status indicating GA is installed as I was currently trying to discern per the help topic? I didn’t really and still don’t know what this is referring to. It’s kinda &lt;span class=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;bushleague.jpg&quot;&gt;bush league&lt;/span&gt; that a company of Google’s caliber repeatedly makes such vague remarks. I even googled to try and figure out what google meant (haha), but its pretty unclear across the board.
So there I was looking at the &lt;code&gt;Tracking Info/ Tracking Code&lt;/code&gt; status message, which said: &lt;span class=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;trackingnotinstalled.png&quot;&gt;Status: Tracking Not Installed&lt;/span&gt;. The next 3 words out of my mouth are the 3 words that no man ever wants to say and/or even think: &lt;span class=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;amiin1.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Am I in?!”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/span&gt; I’m looking at my fucking source code and everything is exactly the way it should be - so what the eff Google!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fast forward &lt;span class=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;amiin.jpg&quot;&gt;2 completely wasted hours of my life&lt;/span&gt; later, after googling trying to figure out about this 24 hour update thing and other googles like “How long does it take for Google Analytics to start working” and “How long does it take for Google Analytics tracking code Status to update” etc. Nada. I even installed Google Analytics Debugger, a super awesome Chrome extension for debugging GA, and, to the best of my pretty decent reasoning abilities, what I was seeing looked like GA was installed:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/chromedebugger.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;chrome debugger screen shot&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet, there I was on my GA account looking at the same &lt;code&gt;Not Installed&lt;/code&gt; (last checked at &lt;code&gt;Time.Now&lt;/code&gt;) message.&lt;br /&gt;
It wasn’t until I read through &lt;a href=&quot;https://productforums.google.com/forum/#!topic/analytics/EZlRmgOCRew&quot;&gt;this entire message thread&lt;/a&gt; where some dude was having an actual installation problem, but then some other dude was having second-guessing syndrome like myself and finally the moderator said the following:&lt;br /&gt; “The tracking status check is a separate check done by the system. It doesn’t update automatically the moment you install the tracking code
It can take a few hours up to 36hrs (and some platforms it can even take up to 72hrs).
Sometimes it doesn’t update at all even when the code is obviously installed and working and data has begun to appear in your account.”&lt;br /&gt;
Duuude! Maaaybe it should say that somewhere near the tracking message status instead of saying directly underneath it that it was last checked at exactly the current time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Still having a panic attack because you really still haven’t technically verified that your shit is working? The best thing to do, &lt;a href=&quot;https://productforums.google.com/forum/#!topic/analytics/EZlRmgOCRew&quot;&gt;as the moderator finally advises&lt;/a&gt;, is to go on to your blog, and then log onto your GA account and then go to reporting, real-time and you will see your little old lonely self as the &lt;code&gt;1 active users&lt;/code&gt; (c’mon google - no dynamic pluralization?!) on your site ☺&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway, its super easy to create and implement GA. And, if you &lt;span class=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;amiin.jpg&quot;&gt;feel like you’re in, you are. 100% of the time in&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2014 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/2014/07/21/am-i-in/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/2014/07/21/am-i-in/</guid>
        
        <category>code</category>
        
        <category>google</category>
        
        <category>analytics</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Who&#39;s the Real CatMan?</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;“Do you have a dog?” Asked the woman in the elevator. &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;twocats.jpg&quot;&gt;“No. I have 2 cats.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
“Oh,” she exclaimed and exchanged aroused glances with her friend. “It’s hard to find a good &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;cat man&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;…” &lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wasn’t always a CatMan though. It’s been a long journey to get here (and I’ve got an even longer journey ahead). Let me give you the high-level stack-trace though.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I guess it all started in a boardroom in Shanghai. I was sitting across the table from a portly Chinese entrepreneur who was saying something to the effect of “Life, is all about creation.” And I thought, &lt;em&gt;YES&lt;/em&gt;! I subsequently quit my job in finance, moved back to NYC, and started up &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.shopcube.com&quot;&gt;ShopCube.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That first year was cinematic. I had absolutely no idea what I was doing. Everyday was 20-hour-days that felt like the last 30 minutes of Zero Dark Thirty – &lt;span class=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;zdt.jpg&quot;&gt;where you know that Osama is gonna get wacked but the suspense of &lt;em&gt;is this shit happening for real&lt;/em&gt; is eating away at your skin…&lt;/span&gt; Well, it was happening for real, and it was exhilarating. I quickly discovered that taking a company from inception, to launching it with a 15,000 user-base, and doubling that user-base in the first year, all without spending a dollar on marketing got me FIRED UP - you know, &lt;span class=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;sienna.gif&quot;&gt;never need to sleep because life is so good you can taste it in your spit&lt;/span&gt; - FIRED UP.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But I will be the first to admit that I, we, made a lot of mistakes. Too many to list. The majority of them were honest, naïve inefficiencies that we were able to address and overcome with relative ease. One crucial error in judgment, however, the negative consequences of which we are still dealing with, was the decision to outsource our development. It seems reasonable right? Neither my partner nor I had a technical background and our third partner, the CTO, lived in Israel and was confident that his Israeli team was comparable to any local talent at a quarter of the price. &lt;span class=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;cake-eating.jpg&quot;&gt;Sweet I thought&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Outsourcing development is singlehandedly responsible for nearly every serious pain point we’ve had at ShopCube. As a result of outsourcing development we were at the mercy of the Israeli dev team’s timetable, which was always at least 4-5x what they estimated. Communication, when even possible, was a never-ending source of frustration. If the site crashed, which a newly launched site of ShopCube’s complexity obviously did, we had little-to-no recourse. But none of these problems would or did sink us. They cost us a great deal of physical, financial, and emotional resources, but I don’t consider them the &lt;em&gt;real&lt;/em&gt; evil in outsourcing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When we parted ways with our CTO and moved development to the US, I took over managing the development team. While it was a step in the right direction in almost every sense and helped address all of the pain points I just mentioned, it still failed to address what became obvious to me as the real evil in outsourcing development – inevitable lack of control.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Outsourcing development is like being a customer in your own restaurant. That sounds insane, right? Imagine asking someone to invest in a restaurant you’re opening and then telling him or her that &lt;span class=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;homer.jpg&quot;&gt;you don’t know how to cook&lt;/span&gt;. As skilled a project manager, as effective a marketer, as efficient an optimizer, as creative a designer as I may be, ultimately these skills would be delegated to a product being created by someone else, someone else with inherently less passion and motivation. The tangible consequences of this are an inability to meaningfully contribute to all important technical debates and decisions. You can say, “I want this feature” and listen to the feasibility, the different potential implementations and their estimates, but you can’t really contribute. This means that a large portion of the decisions that arguably affect your product more than anything else are not being made by you. No matter how &lt;span class=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;food.jpg&quot;&gt;brilliant a vision you have for your restaurant’s menu&lt;/span&gt;, the food that comes out of the kitchen won’t be executed exactly the way you want. With such a razor thin line between success and failure in any venture do you really want to roll the dice leaving your company’s fate in the hands of someone being paid by the hour?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Life, is all about creation,” said the Chinese entrepreneur. Not “half-assed creation”, but “creation.” I helped create the start of what could be something truly incredibly at ShopCube. But I failed to be a part of some of the most important steps in its creation and I refuse to live a life of half-assed creation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Acting on this realization, I began to learn my way around the kitchen and almost a year later, after over 1,500 hours preparing for and immersed in a programming school called &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.devbootcamp.com&quot;&gt;Dev Bootcamp&lt;/a&gt;, I am proud to call myself an engineer. Not a customer in my own Kitchen, but a chef. Not a guy who owns cats, but &lt;span class=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;catman.jpg&quot;&gt;a CatMan&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Life really is all about creation. The technical debt of my outsourced predecessors is significant, but its exhilarating and satisfying to recreate our product and be intimately involved in every decision that goes into it. And this is only the very very beginning, the absolute tip of the iceberg and a hundred other clichés. There is so much I want to create now that sometimes I feel like I’m going to explode.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway, I’m really glad you’re here at the beginning with me. &lt;span class=&quot;tooltip&quot; title=&quot;chuck-norris-uzis.jpg&quot;&gt;It’s going to be one hell of a ride!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2014 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/2014/07/01/who-is-the-real-cat-man/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/2014/07/01/who-is-the-real-cat-man/</guid>
        
        <category>cats</category>
        
        <category>startups</category>
        
        <category>shopcube</category>
        
        <category>outsourcing</category>
        
        <category>devbootcamp</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
